Guide to the John William Davis Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
John William Davis papers
1846-1959
MS 170
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
92.25
The papers consist of correspondence, speeches and writings, diaries, photographs, extensive material from the presidential campaign of 1924, and material relating to John W. Davis's law practice and public activities. Correspondence makes up two-thirds of the papers including early letters by Davis to his family and his first wife, and letters while ambassador to Great Britain (1918-1923). The largest part of the correspondence is for the period 1924-1955 and concerns Davis's civic and political activities. Papers relating to his law practice in New York, where he was counsel to J.P. Morgan and Co., and others are separately arranged. His service as Solicitor General of the United States (1913-19180 is documented only by printed matter with his marginalia. Also in the papers are research materials and drafts by William H. Harbaugh for his biography of Davis, published in 1973.
Davis, John W. (John William), 1873-1955
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Charles Healy, 1961; and William Harbaugh, 1994, 1997; transfer from Circulation Department, SML, 1997.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Existence and Location of Copies
Correspondence, clippings, diaries, and printed matter available on microfilm (4,203 frames on 4 reels, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM84.
Pathe News film of John W. Davis and the Boy Scouts available on microfilm (1,000 frames on 1 reel, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM99.
Arrangement
Arranged in eleven series and two additions: I.1846-1918; II.1918-1921; III.Correspondence, 1921-1923; IV.Correspondence, 1924-1955; V.Presidential Campaign; VI.Speeches and Writings; VII.Law Practice; VIII.Civic and Professional Activities; IX.Harbaugh Biography; X.Writings of others; XI.Personal and Miscellaneous Papers.
Scope and Contents
The John W. Davis Papers consist of ninety feet of correspondence, writings, diaries, photographs, printed matter, and miscellaneous working papers spanning from 1846 to 1959. The papers are arranged in eleven series: I 1846-1918, II 1918-192, III CORRESPONDENCE, 1921-1923, IV CORRESPONDENCE, 1924-1955, V PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN, VI SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, VII LAW PRACTICE, VIII CIVIC AND PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES, IX HARBAUGH BIOGRAPHY, X WRITINGS OF OTHERS, XI PERSONAL AND MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS.
The papers in Series I, II, III, and V are fully processed. The remainder are only roughly organized.
Series I, 1846-1918, contains all the papers related to Davis and his family before he became Ambassador to Great Britain except for speeches (in Series VI) and photographs and clippings (in Series XI). Two-thirds of this series is correspondence, consisting mainly of Davis's letters to members of his family between 1888 and 1918. There is hardly any professional correspondence, but Davis often discussed his work in family letters. The other papers in this series are miscellaneous items belonging to Davis, his father, and his first wife. This includes a diary and miscellaneous working papers related to Davis's participation in the conference on prisoners of war in 1918.
Series II, 1918-1921, contains all the papers related to Davis's ambassadorship except for speeches (in Series VI) and photographs, clippings, and memorabilia (in Series XI). The papers are arranged in three sections: correspondence, special files, and diaries. Most of the letters except those to Emma Kennedy Davis and Frank L. Polk are trivial social communications, but the diaries are compensatingly rich in description of Davis's activities as ambassador. The special files consist of diplomatic memoranda, engagement books, and printed mementoes of ceremonial occasions.
Series III, CORRESPONDENCE, 1921-1923, and Series IV, CORRESPONDENCE, 1924-1955, consist mainly of letters related to Davis's activities other than his private law practice. There is additional correspondence filed by topic in Series VII, VIII, and XI.
Series V, PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN, consists of memoranda, research material, clippings, speeches, and miscellaneous items. There are campaign photographs in Series XI.
Series VI, SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, consists of manuscript and printed versions of speeches, public statements, and writings for publication. Davis's presidential campaign speeches are in Series V. His father's political writings are in Series I.
Series VII, LAW PRACTICE, consists of a small amount of correspondence and documents related to Davis's service as Solicitor General and his private practice in New York. The period of government service is represented only by printed material, some of which, however, has Davis's annotations. The few inches of correspondence were selected and arranged by William H. Harbaugh. There may be additional correspondence related to legal matters in Series I, III, and IV.
Series VIII, CIVIC AND PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES, consists of reports, minutes, memoranda, and miscellaneous working papers related to Davis's service on boards and committees of organizations dedicated to philanthropy, civic betterment, and the advancement of the legal profession. There is significant correspondence connected with the American Foundation and the Carnegie Endowment (including the matter of Alger Hiss), but most of the letters related to these activities are in Series III and IV.
Series IX, HARBAUGH BIOGRAPHY, consists of notes and research material gathered by William H. Harbaugh in preparation for his biography of Davis. The photostatic copies of original letters included in these files are all duplicated elsewhere in the Davis Papers.
Series X, WRITINGS OF OTHERS, consists of manuscript and softbound printed material that Davis received from correspondents or collected in the course of his professional and civic activities. The principal concentrations of printed material are publications of the League of Women Voters and the New York State Bar Association in the 1930s.
Series XI, PERSONAL AND MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS, contains personal subject files, newspaper clippings, biographical material, datebooks, photographs, scrapbooks, and memorabilia. The subject files deal mainly with Davis's health and finances and the celebration of his eightieth birthday. The newspaper clippings, both loose and mounted in scrapbooks, span his entire career but are especially abundant for the 1910s and early 1920s. The photographs, ranging from snapshots to studio portraits, likewise span his entire career, and there are pictures of friends, family, and public gatherings as well as of Davis alone.
The John W. Davis Papers were given to Yale University Library by Davis's daughter, Julia Davis Adams, who also made a donation to pay for preservation of carbon copies of outgoing letters. Much of the collection was in the hands of William H. Harbaugh while he was preparing his biography, and he included his own research material when he passed on the papers to Yale.
Biographical / Historical
John William Davis received his L.L.B. in 1895 and began practicing law. He was elected to Congress from West Virginia in 1910 and 1912. Davis was solicitor general of the United States from 1913-1918 and ambassador to Great Britain from 1918-1921. He was the Democratic candidate for president in 1924.
Campaign literature, 1920 -- Democratic; International relations; Law; Europe; Great Britain -- Foreign relations -- United States; Southern States; United States -- Foreign relations -- Great Britain; United States -- Politics and government; Diaries; Photographs; Lawyers; Andrews, Matthew Page, 1879-1947; Astor, Nancy Witcher Langhorne Astor, Viscountess, 1879-1964; Baruch, Bernard M. (Bernard Mannes), 1870-1965; Battle, George Gordon, 1868-; Beck, James M. (James Montgomery), 1861-1936; Bedford, Alfred Cotton, 1864-1925; Bok, Edward William, 1863-1930; Bullitt, Wm. Marshall (William Marshall), 1873-1957; Cornwell, John J. (John Jacob), 1867-1953; Coudert, Frederic R. (Frederic René), 1832-1903; Cox, James M. (James Middleton), 1870-1957; Craigmyle, Thomas Shaw, Baron, 1850-1937; Davis, Emma Kennedy; Davis, John W. (John William), 1873-1955; Davis, Julia; Edwards, Agustín, 1878-1941; Ewing, Thomas, 1862-1942; Guthrie, William D. (William Dameron), 1859-1935; Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1894-1956; Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928; Nesbitt, Wallace, 1858-; Preston, Walter Creigh, 1895-; Shelton, Thomas W. (Thomas Wall), 1870-1931; Taylor, C. Burgess; Templeton, E. Bryan; Vance, William Reynolds, 1870-1940; Warburg, Paul M. (Paul Moritz), 1868-1932; Wickersham, George W. (George Woodward), 1858-1936; American Bar Association; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company; Carnegie Endowment for International Peace; Council on Foreign Relations; Democratic Party (U.S.); English-Speaking Union
- 1846-(1872-1918), Series I; 3 linear feet (7 boxes, 1 folio)
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of correspondence and miscellaneous papers. The correspondence is in chronological order. The miscellaneous papers are in this order: John J. Davis, John W. Davis, Julia Terrill (McDonald) Davis, conference on prisoners of war. There are speeches from this period in Series VI and photographs, clippings, and memorabilia in Series XI.
  - Correspondence
    - 1871-1897 October (Box 1, Folder 1-13)
    - 1897 November - 1898 September (Box 2, Folder 14-24)
    - 1898 October-Dec, undated, 1899 January-Dec, undated,1900-1902 (Box 3, Folder 25-36)
    - 1903-1915 (Box 4, Folder 37-46)
    - 1916-1918, undated (Box 5, Folder 47-53)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1918
    - A-E (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - F-K (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - L-Q (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - R-T (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - U-Z and unidentified (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Oversize (Box 6, Folder 58)
    General
    See: box 197
  - Miscellany
    - Davis, John J.
      - Address, "Evils of War", 1846 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Letter from his father (copy), [1854] (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Speech in the House of Representatives re: amendments to the Constitution (printed), 1872 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Speech in the House of Representatives re: civil rights (printed), 1874 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Speech in the House of Representatives re: federal intervention in the states, 1875 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Speech re: the national debt, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - Speech at the Harrison County Democratic convention, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - Speech re: the Democratic platform, [1896] (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Speech re: the distribution of wealth, [1896] (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Speech … Delivered at Weston, W. Va., 1898 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Letter … to C. P. Howell, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Letter … to R. U. True, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Why We Are Democrats and What We Believe, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Editorials of the Clarksburg News (reprint), 1907 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Speech … at Banquet of the Marshall County Democratic Club, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Speech … at Banquet of the Marshall County Democratic Club, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Speech, "Republican Consistency: The Income Tax vs. Protectionism", undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Speech re: the nature of the federal government (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Speech re: the Fifteenth Amendment (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Fragmentary and unidentified writings, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - Davis & Walker business card, undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Davis, John W.
      - Compositions and notes, 1883-1884, undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Grade reports, 1885-1892 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Program and invitation from Pantops, Academy (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Personal record books, 1888-1889, [1889-1892?] (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Social invitations and programs, 1880-1896, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - School notes, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Commencement program, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Address to the Class of 1892, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - "Law Class Oration," The Southern Collegian, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - Bankbook, 1894-1895 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Law school examinations, 1895-1897 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Law school "time book", 1896-1897 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Law notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - Financial papers, 1911-1917 (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - Account and appointment books, 1912-1917 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1913-1915, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Davis, Julia Terrill (McDonald)
      - Compositions, 1889-1892, undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - Diary, 1892 January 1-1898 October 7 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - Notes and invitation for wedding, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - Memorial booklet, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Conference on prisoners of war
      - Diary, 1918 August 23-November 26 (Box 7, Folder 93)
      - Notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
      - Letters and memoranda, 1918 July 31-August 29, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
      - Minutes (mimeo), 1918 September 24-November 11 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      - Reports, outlines, and drafts (typescript, some annotated, mainly carbon), 1918, undated (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Regulations and forms used in American camps, 1918, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Printed matter, 1918, undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
- 1918-1921, Series II; 2.5 linear feet (6 boxes)
  This series consists of correspondence, special files, and diaries in that order. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically. There are speeches from this period in Series VI and photographs, clippings, and memorabilia in Series XI.
  - Correspondence
    - A-F, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - G-L, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - M-Z, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Aglionby Charles E., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Aglionby F. K., 1918, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Aglionby J. B., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, George M., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, Joshua W., 1919 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Henry T., 1921 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - American Bar Association, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - American Luncheon Club, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - American Society in London, The, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Arthur William Patrick Albert, duke of Connaught, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Ashfield, Albert Henry Stanley, 1st baron, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Asquith, Herbert Henry (1st earl of Oxford and Asquith), 1919 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Asquith, Emma Alice Margaret (Tennant), 1918 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Astor, John Jacob, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Astor, Nancy Witcher (Langhorne) Astor, viscountess, 1919,1921 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Astor, Waldorf Astor, 2nd viscount, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Athlone, Alexander Augustus Frederick William Alfred George Cambridge, 1st earl of, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Auchincloss, Gordon, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Baker, Newton Diehl, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Balfour, Arthur James, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Barratt, John Arthur, 1919, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Baruch, Bernard Mannes (Box 8, Folder 9)
      See: box 1
    - Bassell, Rebecca Benedict, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Beck, James M., 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bell, Edward, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Benedum, Michael Late, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Berryman, Clifford Kennedy, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Biddle, John, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Birkenhead, Frederick Edwin Smith, 1st earl of, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bisbee, Eldon, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bland, William T., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bliss, Tasker H., 1919 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Borden, Sir Robert Laird, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brand, Robert Henry, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brandeis, Louis Dembitz, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brittain, Sir Harry E. (Box 8, Folder 12)
      See: box 10, folder 63
    - Britton, Alexander, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brooks, Sydney, 1918, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Izetta Jewel, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bryce of Dechmont, James Bryce, 1st viscount, 1918-1921 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Buckler, William Hepburn, 1919, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Buckmaster, Stanley Owen Buckmaster, 1st baron, 1919, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Buffham, John H., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Bullitt, William H., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Burdett-Coutts, William Lehman Ashmead Bartlett, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Burnham, Harry Lawson Webster Lawson, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Byington, F. D., 1919 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Campbell, Henry Donald, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Carlin, Gaston, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Carnegie, William Hartley, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Carson, Sir Edward, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Cecil of Chelwood, Edgar Algernon Robert Cecil, 1st viscount, 1919, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Chamberlin, Frederick, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Charnwood, Godfrey Rathbone Benson, 1st baron, 1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Chinda, Sutemi, count, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Churchill, Sir Winston (Leonard Spencer), 1919, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Clayton, Henry D., 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Colby, Bainbridge, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Coleridge, Bernard John Seymour Coleridge, 2nd baron, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Cornwell, John J., 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Cox, James Middleton, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Cravath, Paul D., 1918, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Crewe, Robert Offley Ashburton Crewe-Milnes, 1st marquis of, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Curzon of Kedleston, George Nathaniel Curzon, 1st earl of, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Daniels, Josephus, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Darling of Langham, Charles John Darling, 1st baron, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Davis, C. J., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Emma Kennedy, 1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Julia McDonald, 1918-1920 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Norman H., 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Davison, Henry Pomeroy, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Desborough, William Henry Grenfell, 1st baron, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Drummond, Sir (James) Eric, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Dulles, Allen Welsh, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Dulles, John Foster, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Dumont, Frederick T. F., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Edwards, Agustin, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Evans, Lynden, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Ewing, James W., 1918, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Ewing, Thomas, 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Filene, Edward A., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Finlay of Nairn, Robert Bannatyne Finlay, 1st viscount, 1919-1921 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Finley, J. B., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fleming, Archibald, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fleming, Robert and K. (Mrs. Robert), 1919 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Forbes, J. Grant, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Francis, David R., 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Garrett, John Work, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Garrison, Lindley Miller, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Gary, Hampson, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Gay, Edwin Francis, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Geddes, Sir Eric (Campbell), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - George V, King of Great Britain, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - George VI, King of Great Britain, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Gerry, Peter Goelet, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Glasgow, Arthur Graham, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Glass, carter, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Goff, Guy Despard, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Goldsmith, Robert, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Grady, Henry Francis, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Graham, Samuel Jordan, 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Gray's Inn, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Grayson, Cary Travers, 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Gregory, Charles Noble, 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Gregory, Stephen Strong, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Gregory, Thomas Watt, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Grew, Joseph Clark, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Grey of Fallodon, Edward Grey, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Grigg, Sir Edward William Macleay, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Griscom, Lloyd Carpenter, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Grouitch, Mabel (Dunlop), 1918, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Gunther, Franklin Mott, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Hadfield, Sir Robert A., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Haldane of Cloan, Richard Burdon Haldane, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Halley, Samuel H., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Hamilton, John M'Lure, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Hamlin, Charles Sumner, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Hankey, Sir Maurice Pascal Alers, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Harcourt, William Edward Harcourt, 2nd viscount, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Harding, Warren G., 1921 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Hardinge of Penshurst, Charles Hardinge, 1st baron, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Harmsworth, Cecil Bisshopp, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Harrison, Francis Burton, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Harvey, George Brinton McClellan, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Hayashi, Gonsuke, baron, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Henry William Frederick Albert, duke of Gloucester, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Herter, Christian Archibald, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Hewart of Bury, Gordon Hewart, 1st baron, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Higgins, Edwin W., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Horne, Sir Robert, (Stevenson), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Horner, Lynn S., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - House, Edward Mandell, 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Houston, Hale, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hughes, William J., 1918 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Hunt, Gaillard, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Imperiali, Guglielmo, marquis, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Johnston, J. W., 1918-1920, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Jones, Sir Roderick, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine Jules, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Keppel, Sir Derek, [1919?] (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Kernan, Francis Joseph, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Koontz, Arthur B., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Lamar, William H., 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Lamont, Thomas William, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Lang, Cosmo Gordon Lang, baron, Abp. of Canterbury, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Lansing, Eleanor (Mrs. Robert) [to Ellen(Bassell) Davis], 1919-1920 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1918-1919 November (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1919 December-1920 March (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Lansing, Robert, 1920 April-1921 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - László de Lombos, Philip Alexius, 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Laughlin, Irwin Boyle, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Lee of Fareham, Arthur Hamilton Lee, 1st viscount, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Lee, Sir Sidney, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Lincoln, Robert Todd (Box 9, Folder 52)
      See: box 10, folder 84
    - Lipton, Sir Thomas Johnstone, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Lloyd George, David, 1918-1919 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Loucheur, Louis, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 53)